<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Resume>
  <FullName>Potjamarn (Yui) Arpornratn</FullName>
  <AddressLine1>25235 SE Klahanie Blvd., </AddressLine1>
  <AddressLine2>STE A-204</AddressLine2>
  <City>Issaquah</City>
  <State>WA</State>
  <PostalCode>98029</PostalCode>
  
  <Educations>
    <Institution>University of Oregon
      <GraduatedMonth>June</GraduatedMonth>
      <GraduatedYear>1997</GraduatedYear>
      <Degree>BS</Degree>
      <Major>Computer Information Science</Major>
      <Minor></Minor>
    </Institution>

    <Institution>Assumption University
      <GraduatedMonth>March</GraduatedMonth>
      <GraduatedYear>1992</GraduatedYear>
      <Degree>BA</Degree>
      <Major>Business Administration (Marketing)</Major>
      <Minor></Minor>
    </Institution>
  </Educations>
  
  <Experiences>
    <companyName>Ascents Services Group
      <fromYear>06/2012</fromYear>
      <toYear>08/2012</toYear>
      <jobTitle>Senior SDET</jobTitle>
      <jobDescriptions>
        Responsible for solving complex testing challenges with an emphasis on automation and quality processes.
        Partner with the Scrum team to plan, write, execute and refactor manual and automated test cases to provide story coverage. Pair programming on test and production code.
        Implement test code within a best-fit automation framework.
      </jobDescriptions>
    </companyName>

    <companyName>InfoSys
      <fromYear>02/2012</fromYear>
      <toYear>06/2012</toYear>
      <jobTitle>Technical Test Lead (Senior SDET)</jobTitle>
      <jobDescriptions>
        Participate in discussions with customers to gather scope information and perform analysis of scope information in order to provide inputs for project scope documentation
        Participate in requirement elicitation process defined in the project management plan to identify requirement gaps/issues (both functional and non-functional) in order to come up with a comprehensive requirement document
        Perform high and Low level design , provides pseudo codes, Implements the prototypes and does design reviews in order to deliver design documents as per customer requirements
        Mentor the team in Technical Competencies and provides performance feedback of the individual team member to the Project Manager in order to manage performance
      </jobDescriptions>
    </companyName>

    <companyName>Staffing Technology (Short-term contract for ING Direct)
      <fromYear>12/2011</fromYear>
      <toYear>01/2012</toYear>
      <jobTitle>Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET)</jobTitle>
      <jobDescriptions>
        Member of IT Department (back office QA Analysts):  Design, develop, and execute test plans and test cases for client server applications, and system upgrades
        Design and develop automation for data generation, regression, and application testing for internal integration applications (backend testing via SQL Store procedures).
        Develop test strategy and create and execute test cases for applications that integrate with external vendor systems.
      </jobDescriptions>
    </companyName>
    
  </Experiences>
  
</Resume>


